<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<candidates>
<candidate id="0"><url>https://djinni.co//q/31b722c2af/</url><position>Web Developer</position><locations quantity="2"><value>Remote work</value><value>Russia</value></locations><salary>2000</salary><years_of_experience>5</years_of_experience><english_level>Pre-Intermediate</english_level><experience /><skills quantity="13"><value>JavaScript</value><value>Joomla</value><value>jQuery</value><value>PHP</value><value>REST API</value><value>Phalcon</value><value>HTML</value><value>CSS</value><value>MySQL</value><value>Bootstrap</value><value>MVC</value><value>Git</value><value>Sphinx</value></skills><highlights /><expectations /></candidate>
<candidate id="1"><url>https://djinni.co//q/7be7db037f/</url><position>Full stack developer</position><locations quantity="1"><value>Kyiv</value></locations><salary>2500</salary><years_of_experience>4</years_of_experience><english_level>Upper Intermediate</english_level><experience>- 2015-17 ISD. Fist working experience, started from a small Desktop Application project although in a while moved onto internal web project for recruitment purposes. Which started as a monolith web app on AngularJS + ASP.Net Web API 2 + MS SQL (EF 6) and shortly moved to VueJS + NetCore 1.2-2.0 + MS SQL (EF Core) with Microservice architecture. Was responsible for different parts of the application, frontend, backend, architecture designing, DevOps, pull-request validation, etc.- 2017 "SOLVVE". Bloodbank healthcare project was needed to be built with a modern web application approach, while execution should run on top of old ASCI terminal service with closed sourced custom exchange protocol. Techs: Angular + NetCore 2.1. Backend position.- 2018 "AMC Bridge". PLM Solution "Aras", worked mostly on a standalone add-on for the main project dedicated to organising effectivity of project lifecycle. Primarily was responsible for plain JavaScript ES5+ client-side logic with slight work on C# API modules- 2019 1st half "Centre de Nanosciences et de Nanotechnologies" (C2N) of Paris-Saclay. Intern researcher at the lab of Paris-Saclay. Research in the domain of bioinformatics, using graph/network theory and data processing technics to analyse structures of macromolecular units (Ribosomes, DNA, RNA, etc). Mostly Python programming.- 2019 2nd half "Know Your Customer". Member of the remotely distributed team on the position of C# SDE and partially as Python Machine Learning Engineer. ASP.Net MVC, Azure, Azure Service Bus, Hangfire, Microservice arch. Responsible for data exchange improvements and OCR detection microservice.</experience><skills quantity="29"><value>Design Patterns</value><value>Git</value><value>OOP</value><value>.NET</value><value>C#</value><value>Entity Framework</value><value>LINQ</value><value>MVC</value><value>ASP.NET</value><value>JavaScript</value><value>MSSQL</value><value>REST</value><value>asp.net mvc</value><value>Redis</value><value>.NET Core</value><value>.Asp.Net Core</value><value>Asp.Net WepApi</value><value>Python</value><value>F#</value><value>MS SQL Server</value><value>REST API</value><value>SOLID</value><value>HTML</value><value>CSS</value><value>ReactJS</value><value>Microservices</value><value>SQL</value><value>TDD</value><value>SPA</value></skills><highlights>Master of Applied Math, Ukraine.Master of Computer Science (NLP/ML), FranceMentorship on several courses. Leadership skills.Involvement into scientific researches. Awards on computer science competitions and active hackaton member previously.</highlights><expectations>I would like to work with recent stack of .Net, it means .Net Core, not Full Framework.Full-Stack roles are okay while most of my work remains on backend. Possibly NodeJs. If more frontend I would prefer projects with ReactJs.No Oracle, no java, no ruby, no python backend. I just don't find myself comfortable with them.Expect openness from company I am going to work on, means mutual-trust, freedom and flexibility.GameDev related is huge plus.</expectations></candidate>
<candidate id="2"><url>https://djinni.co//q/f1fa7fb2b3/</url><position>iOS Developer</position><locations quantity="2"><value>Bud'-jakij</value><value>Kyiv</value></locations><salary>1600</salary><years_of_experience>2</years_of_experience><english_level>Upper Intermediate</english_level><experience>Organized, collaborative, and highly motivated iOS developer with 2.5 years of professional experience in dynamic and deadline-driven work environments. Able to analyse problems, find solutions and implement them. Orderly, purposeful, learn with ease. I also understand the importance of creating highly readable and easily maintainable source code. I am constantly striving to learn new technologies and look to ways to better myself in this rapidly changing industry.</experience><skills quantity="16"><value>iOS</value><value>Xcode</value><value>Swift</value><value>Objective-C</value><value>Foundation</value><value>UIKit</value><value>Multithreading</value><value>GCD</value><value>Autolayout</value><value>REST API</value><value>MVC</value><value>SOLID</value><value>OOP</value><value>Design Patterns</value><value>User Interface </value><value>Git</value></skills><highlights>Worked with Core NFC when it was just released</highlights><expectations>Interesting projects, friendly team, work on result</expectations></candidate>
<candidate id="3"><url>https://djinni.co//q/b87efaaae2/</url><position>UX/UI Designer</position><locations quantity="1"><value>Kyiv</value></locations><salary>700</salary><years_of_experience>1</years_of_experience><english_level>Intermediate</english_level><experience>Выполняла дизайн интерфейсов и разрабатывала прототипы для приложений, а также по надобности выполняла индивидуальные Ui решения для заказчиков. Использовала Figma, Illustrator, XD, Photoshop.При этом активно интересовалась психологией клиента, маркетингом, чтобы помочь сделать удобные сайт/приложение, которые будут работать.По мимо веб дизайна желаю изучать язык программирования JavaScript.</experience><skills quantity="24"><value>Figma</value><value>UI/UX</value><value>User Interface</value><value>Adobe Illustrator</value><value>Wireframes</value><value>Prototype</value><value>WEB DESIGN</value><value>Adobe XD</value><value>MockFlow</value><value>Wireframe</value><value>Website designer</value><value>InVision</value><value>User interview</value><value>Design System</value><value>User Experience</value><value>mobile design</value><value>User communication</value><value>mobile</value><value>Design thinking</value><value>Jira</value><value>Design Processes</value><value>Prototyping</value><value>Design Patterns</value><value>UI / UX</value></skills><highlights>Мой опыт в веб дизайне заключается в сотрудничестве с европейскими компаниями и США (фриланс, удаленно). Самый первый серьезный проект, который мне очень запомнился - это сайт для немецкой стоматологии "Wunchlachen", который я выполнила и он пришелся по вкусу заказчику. Мне это удалось, при полном отсутствии знаний немецкого языка. Хочу подчеркнуть, что я с большим удовольствием решаю сложные задачи и быстро обучаюсь.</highlights><expectations>Готова сотрудничать  с зарубежными компаниями, но не предпочтительно. Если вы находитесь не в Киеве, то возьму удалённую работу.Желаю, чтобы в компании была возможность развиваться, уважительное отношение к сотрудникам, выполнение договоренностей и достойная оплата.</expectations></candidate>
<candidate id="4"><url>https://djinni.co//q/028d3ff937/</url><position>Frontend Developer (Vue)</position><locations quantity="1"><value>Kyiv</value></locations><salary>3500</salary><years_of_experience>4</years_of_experience><english_level>Upper Intermediate</english_level><experience>Last 4+ years I was:- Developing web applications (landing, e-commerce, corporate site, SPA)- Creating projects boilerplate and architecture - Crafting smooth animations with CSS, SVG, canvas- Leading team and making code review- Interviewing new developers and mentoring juniors</experience><skills quantity="9"><value>HTML</value><value>CSS</value><value>JavaScript</value><value>Node.js</value><value>Vue.js</value><value>Nuxt</value><value>SASS/SCSS</value><value>Webpack</value><value>Git</value></skills><highlights>- published couple npm packages with 30k+ downloads- created fluent desktop and touch interfaces with amazing animations- set up team’s code style from scratch</highlights><expectations>Challenging frontend tasks, friendly team, experienced team lead or architect. Vue.js - desirable framework.</expectations></candidate>
<candidate id="5"><url>https://djinni.co//q/e150545e/</url><position>Senior QA Engineer manual/automation</position><locations quantity="1"><value>Kyiv</value></locations><salary>3200</salary><years_of_experience>7</years_of_experience><english_level>Advanced/Fluent</english_level><experience>Experience on different projects with different technologies.* Preparing and maintaining testing documentation.* Experience in setup automation process from scratch;* Experience in different types of testing: functional, regression/acceptance, integration testing, performance/load/stress, automation etc.* Technologies: SOAP, REST, SQL, Oracle, Selenium WebDriver, client-server architecture, microservices architecture. * Automation frameworks: Cucumber BDD + Java, Appium, Espresso.* Business Analysis Fundamentals.* Soft skills: communication with customers/product owners, process integration and improvements, experience in QA activities coordination,</experience><skills quantity="66"><value>Manual Testing (QA)</value><value>MSSQL</value><value>MySQL</value><value>Selenium</value><value>Automated Testing (QA)</value><value>Oracle</value><value>Selenium WebDriver</value><value>Java</value><value>C#</value><value>Quality Assurance</value><value>Regression Testing</value><value>Functional testing</value><value>Scrum</value><value>SQL</value><value>Web Testing</value><value>Jira</value><value>Manual Testing</value><value>Confluence</value><value>Quality Assurance </value><value>Security</value><value>Postman</value><value>HTML</value><value>CSS</value><value>Agile</value><value>Test documentation writing/maintenance</value><value>TestNG</value><value>Docker</value><value>JMeter</value><value>Test methodology</value><value>Function Testing</value><value>Cross Browser Testing</value><value>Functional</value><value>Automated Testing </value><value>Requirements analysis/clarification</value><value>STLC</value><value>JUnit</value><value>Git</value><value>Requirement Management</value><value>JSON</value><value>e2e testing</value><value>Cucumber</value><value>XML</value><value>XPath</value><value>Maven</value><value>REST API</value><value>Jenkins</value><value>Automated Testing</value><value>IntelliJ IDEA</value><value>Manual Testing </value><value>Linux</value><value>OOP</value><value>Page Object Pattern</value><value>GUI testing</value><value>API testing</value><value>Confluence/Wiki</value><value>Test Planning &amp;amp;amp; Documentation</value><value>Android</value><value>Appium</value><value>TestRail</value><value>SDLC</value><value>Windows</value><value>BDD</value><value>usability</value><value>REST Assured</value><value>API Testing</value><value>Test Documentation</value></skills><highlights>Experience in creating test automation frameworks from scratch.ISTQB foundation certificate.Business Analysis Fundamentals certificate.CSPO certificate by ScrumAlliance</highlights><expectations>Business trips abroad, relocation.</expectations></candidate>
<candidate id="6"><url>https://djinni.co//q/e1cbb5ef52/</url><position>Розробник PHP</position><locations quantity="1"><value>Kyiv</value></locations><salary>400</salary><years_of_experience>0</years_of_experience><english_level>Pre-Intermediate</english_level><experience>Development of Symfony-based web service to automation online bidding process for premium aero services (administration system and client side).Technology: PHP 7.1 + Symfony 3.2 + Doctrine ORM / PDO (PostgreSQL) + Git + Git-CI + phpunit + Composer</experience><skills quantity="11"><value>PHP</value><value>Git</value><value>Linux</value><value>MVC</value><value>HTML</value><value>CSS</value><value>jQuery</value><value>MySQL</value><value>Symfony</value><value>webpack</value><value>Bootstrap</value></skills><highlights>create CRUD and Blog, fixed errors, updated modules, configured tests</highlights><expectations>skills development in PHP</expectations></candidate>
<candidate id="7"><url>https://djinni.co//q/ee79d46701/</url><position>Branding, marketing, copywriting</position><locations quantity="1"><value>Kyiv</value></locations><salary>1200</salary><years_of_experience>10</years_of_experience><english_level>Advanced/Fluent</english_level><experience>Head of content, Brander - 2017-2020-	Making brand content kernels, technical and marketing scrutiny of service/product/company. -	Strategic content planning, blogs, SEO texts, SMM. Working with sales and design. -	Creating companies’ personality, legend, website structure and content, compiling business cases and case studies, work on targeted platforms, promoting in pillar media.  Client  manager - Sportsbetting, 2 yearsThis venture aimed at sportsbetting market in Europe- I was developing relations with the marketing and analysts, made projects, created a 2nd level Support centre.Client manager, Technical writer – 3 yearsI created descriptions of dozen of software products for more than 5000 representative sales office.Functional consultant, Technical writing team lead  - 2 years This company was developing a CMS framework. -	I was showing EU enterprise clients how to construct and set up their websites to meet their business needs, -	held progress and status meetings with writers from Ukraine, Poland and India. Business trips to headquarters, presentations. -	I was making competitive market analysis and recommending site structure and functions to clients, making site progress analysis based on web analytics, generating charts and schemes, recommending functional changes to clients’ websites.</experience><skills quantity="10"><value>Digital marketing</value><value>Marketing</value><value>SEO</value><value>Google Analytics</value><value>Content marketing</value><value>English</value><value>SMM</value><value>Team management</value><value>copywriting</value><value>Web Analytics</value></skills><highlights>The team and me got a license for new sportbetting business. Also, with another team, we won several crowdfundings.</highlights><expectations>I expect creating branded content and leading content marketing.</expectations></candidate>
<candidate id="8"><url>https://djinni.co//q/c399d0cee8/</url><position>Senior PHP Developer</position><locations quantity="1"><value>Kyiv</value></locations><salary>3500</salary><years_of_experience>5</years_of_experience><english_level>Pre-Intermediate</english_level><experience>Интересовался программированием еще в школе, но очевидно в серьез даже говорить не стану об этом опыте. Отсчет можно начинать с 2014 года, с первой работы, как PHP-intern. Практически сразу познакомился с symfony, так с ним и остался по сей день. Первое время были в основном eCommerce решения и небольшие сайтики, с легкими отклонениями от мира PHP на c++/java. Примерно с 2017  занимался поддержкой 2 проектов: платформа для рекрутеров ( агрегация данных из разных источников и ATS в одном)  и "тиндер" для инвесторов (админка и апи для мобильного приложения, с целью автоматизации процесса проведения бизнес форумов), последний разрабатывал с 0.Сейчас интересуюсь GO, и в перспективе готов рассматривать полноценный переход на этот язык. Был опыт собеседованию кандидатов как на бек так и на фронт. Немного помогал младшим коллегам в становлении.</experience><skills quantity="8"><value>PHP</value><value>Symfony</value><value>MySQL</value><value>Elastic Search</value><value>MongoDB</value><value>RabbitMQ</value><value>SOLID</value><value>REST API</value></skills><highlights>Я достаточно самокритичен, и потому не считаю что делал что-то сверхъестественное чем мог бы похвастаться в данном блоке.</highlights><expectations>3 самых главных аспекта: команда, проект, деньги.команда - не хотел бы быть лошадью тянущей повозку из джунов. Интересен обмен опытом сильными специалиста. Конечно при необходимости готов обучать младших. проект - в идеале с 0, но не принципиально. Интересно поработать с микросервисной архитектурой / хайлоуд проектами. Открытость к использованию новых технологий. Не хотелось бы оказаться на полноценной поддержке легаси. Чем сложнее задание - тем сильнее кайф от найденного решения.</expectations></candidate>
<candidate id="9"><url>https://djinni.co//q/a041c16a1d/</url><position>junior java developer</position><locations quantity="1"><value>Kyiv</value></locations><salary>100</salary><years_of_experience>1</years_of_experience><english_level>Pre-Intermediate</english_level><experience /><skills quantity="1"><value>Java</value></skills><highlights>Знання java SE, робота с БД SQL, NOSQL.Базові знання Spring,Досвід роботи з GIT, Maven, Hibernate.... Розробка сервісних додатків, розробка чат-ботів на різну тематику.</highlights><expectations /></candidate>
<candidate id="10"><url>https://djinni.co//q/5d0e57ade1/</url><position>Business Development Manager</position><locations quantity="1"><value>Kyiv</value></locations><salary>1000</salary><years_of_experience>3</years_of_experience><english_level>Upper Intermediate</english_level><experience>Hello, thank you in advance for considering me as a candidate. I'd like to join an IT product company for the position of Business Development Manager or Sales Manager. My key responsibilities on the current and previous jobs are as follows:Generating new prospects according to the geography, industry, company size, etc. and creating a cold database of them;finding new potential clients on LinkedIn, Crunchbase, AngelList, web rankings, etc.;qualifying prospects and initiate engagement via mass email campaigns and LinkedIn connecting;working with outbound (mostly) and inbound leads;developing new strategies to assist sales’ outbound lead generation;working with Google Analytics;creating email and LinkedIn templates for mass as well as personalized campaigns and its further sending;conducting calls with warm leads, showing the presentation via online meetings to potential clients about the company and its services;maintaining a good communication and documentation exchange between Sales Management and client.</experience><skills quantity="26"><value>Sales</value><value>Communication Skills</value><value>English</value><value>B2B</value><value>It sales</value><value>International sales</value><value>Business development</value><value>Lead generation</value><value>Negotiations</value><value>Linkedin</value><value>Business Developement</value><value>Presentation skills</value><value>Team player</value><value>Networking</value><value>Europe and USA markets</value><value>CRM</value><value>Pre-sales</value><value>Client oriented</value><value>fluent English</value><value>E-Marketing</value><value>Good communication skills</value><value>Market analysis</value><value>Effective C-level communication</value><value>Продажи</value><value>Sales Operation</value><value>Analytics</value></skills><highlights>The greatest achievement for me is the process of setting up the sales funnel by myself. I've done it from the very beginning (market research, generating the database of cold prospects, their contacting and further communication). It brought to my company 100 warm leads. There were 30 hot leads among them.</highlights><expectations>I would like to work in a product company as now I am working in a service one and the potential client can't fully understand the offer as it's not something "touchable". He/she can't try it before taking some obligations (for instance, to try a demo). I can work in both cases: in a team and alone. It is always great to have someone near you who can share the experience and give some advice. Also, I like to create everything by myself from zero and then look back and realize how much work was done.</expectations></candidate>
<candidate id="11"><url>https://djinni.co//q/caf6c44c91/</url><position>Senior UI/UX designer</position><locations quantity="1"><value>Kyiv</value></locations><salary>1500</salary><years_of_experience>6</years_of_experience><english_level>Pre-Intermediate</english_level><experience>Hello. Thank you for your interest in my candidacyA little bit about yourself)My name is Sasha, work experience 6 years.Last 2 years working as a Lead Designer at a digital agency.I develop prototypes, websites, applications, logos and various graphics.I approach every new design challenges with an eye on the latest trends and strive to align my work the industry current best practices</experience><skills quantity="14"><value>User Interface</value><value>Adobe Photoshop</value><value>User Experience</value><value>Sketch</value><value>WEB DESIGN</value><value>mobile design</value><value>Illustrator</value><value>Responsive Design</value><value>Design</value><value>Prototype</value><value>Google Material</value><value>Userflows</value><value>Figma</value><value>Tilda</value></skills><highlights>From scratch, and up to the end, designed one of the largest E-commerce projects in the company, which lasted more than a year.With the team, we developed a mobile application with the largest AR quests in Ukraine.Behance Interaction Gallery x2</highlights><expectations>Intresting projects, good team, stability company</expectations></candidate>
<candidate id="12"><url>https://djinni.co//q/34e9b1e6a7/</url><position>HRD, Head of Recruitment</position><locations quantity="1"><value>Kyiv</value></locations><salary>1500</salary><years_of_experience>3</years_of_experience><english_level>Intermediate</english_level><experience>- Полный цикл рекрутинга: ресерч резюме, пре-скриннинг, телефонное интервью, собеседование в офисе, составление оффера;- Закрытие вакансий - Front-end Developer, Full Stack Developer, QA Engineer, Head of Sales, Sales Manager, Retention Manager, Support Manager, Designer, Community Manager, Marketing Manager, Partnership Manager, Lead Generation, Copywriter, Финансовый менеджер, Account Manager, Recruiter, PPC-специалист, SEO-специалист;- Онбординг сотрудников;- Ведение аналитики и отчетности;- Контроль прохождения испытательного срока;- Оценка эффективности сотрудников;- Проведение 1-2-1;- Организация мероприятий, корпоративов;- Сотрудничество с курсами, ВУЗами;- Проведение митингов;- Менторство рекрутеров (3 чел);- Написание инструкций.</experience><skills quantity="16"><value>Interviewing</value><value>Research</value><value>LinkedIn Search</value><value>CV Screening</value><value>Communication</value><value>Human Resources</value><value>Boolean Search</value><value>Onboarding</value><value>Interviews</value><value>Recruiting</value><value>Sourcing</value><value>One to one meetings</value><value>HR interviews</value><value>X-Ray</value><value>Screening candidates</value><value>Screening</value></skills><highlights>1. 93% кандидатов успешно прошли испытательный срок;2. Создала Welcome Book для новых сотрудников;3. Организовала интернатуру для студентов;4. Ввела English Speaking Club с носителями английского из Америки и Британии;5. Создание системы оценки сотрудника;6. Разработка онбординга.</highlights><expectations>1. Возможность удаленной работы 2-3 раза в неделю2. Только продуктовая компания</expectations></candidate>
<candidate id="13"><url>https://djinni.co//q/e0b7500dfc/</url><position>Data Scientist</position><locations quantity="1"><value>Kyiv</value></locations><salary>1700</salary><years_of_experience>1</years_of_experience><english_level>Upper Intermediate</english_level><experience>My main experience is leading three project two of which is computer vision. 1) Prozzoro project - tender`s success prediction. Mostly domain analysis, feature engineering  and transparent algorithms such as decision trees. 2) Parking app for UNIT city which shows available parking spots to user. Solution based on car detector applied to images from security cameras. Pipeline was created from scratch.3) Talking-head. Basically it is more like academic project because the goal was to reproduce the paper. Description: assuming we have a talking-head video (which is framed to focus on the face and upper body of a speaking) and accurate transcript of speech our task was to edit the video given only new transcript (which may include even previously unspoken words). More details in the paper: 1906.01524 on arxiv4) Semantic segmentation project with super unbalanced data. Training DL models, creating pipelines, delivering and communication with customer - main tasks i was responsible for.</experience><skills quantity="5"><value>Python</value><value>Machine Learning</value><value>Data Science</value><value>Deep Learning</value><value>Statistics</value></skills><highlights>Mostly i`m proud about the thing that i was able to lead teams.</highlights><expectations>1) I`m looking for strong tech lead to learn from. 2) I prefer doing projects which needs machine learning algorithms to be used. Don`t like projects about scraping data or creating visual dashboards. Also the idea matters a lot. For example, i hate projects about betting. 3) Big plus for me is having time for learning (i.e one day of week is learning day) or opportunities to discover new technologies.</expectations></candidate>
<candidate id="14"><url>https://djinni.co//q/bdc0682494/</url><position>JavaScript Developer | Front-End</position><locations quantity="2"><value>Remote work</value><value>Ukraine</value></locations><salary>1000</salary><years_of_experience>3</years_of_experience><english_level>Pre-Intermediate</english_level><experience>I am a Frontend Developer, graduateof Automation Computer Integrated Technologies. I have more then 3 years commercial experience providing frontend development, producing high quality responsive websites and exceptional user experience.I have experience in building and supporting applications for mobile devices on the Android and iOS platforms.</experience><skills quantity="9"><value>JavaScript</value><value>Photoshop</value><value>SASS</value><value>Git</value><value>RX.js</value><value>Jira</value><value>TypeScript</value><value>Angular</value><value>HTML</value></skills><highlights>- Front-end development of websites using Angular- Setting up CI/CD on Gitlab- Project Management and Control (Agile )- Identifying and analyzing performance bottlenecks and rectifying them;- Browser extension development</highlights><expectations>- Good team- Clean code- Professional growth- Interesting and long-playing projects</expectations></candidate>
<candidate id="15"><url>https://djinni.co//q/a56af8066c/</url><position>Junior QA Engineer</position><locations quantity="1"><value>Lviv</value></locations><salary>300</salary><years_of_experience>0</years_of_experience><english_level>Pre-Intermediate</english_level><experience>SkillsBasic knowledge of QA software: TestRail, Trello;Basic knowledge of software testing theory;Basic knowledge of HTML &amp;amp; CSS, SQL;Basic knowledge of computer networks;Knowledge of such OS: Windows, Android, iOS LanguagesEnglish- Pre intermediatePoland - elementary Experience Uncomercisl practice within courses OktenWeb University (February- March 2019): web and desktop applications Black-box testing (Functional, Compatibility) writing Checklists, Test Cases, Bug Reports, Test Plan using TestRail, Trello“BeeSmart” online school (May 2018 - January 2019) - office manager“F-Print” (March 2017 - October 2017) - sales manager“Drevny Grad” hotel (November 2013 - December 2016) - sales manager“Galaktika” hotel (April 2012 - November 2013) - administratorEducationTesting QA/QC in OktenWeb University (February- March 2019)Preparatory course QI in SkillUp (November 2018)Lviv State Financial Academy (2001-2006) specialty FinancePersonal infoSociability, punctuality, honesty, diligence, ability to work for a good result.I love books, travels and dogs.</experience><skills quantity="1"><value>Manual Testing</value></skills><highlights>I know that my practical knowledge in testing is very minimal, but I really want to develop in this direction.</highlights><expectations>I hope that I will be able to get on an interesting project where I can grow and develop in QC.</expectations></candidate>
<candidate id="16"><url>https://djinni.co//q/10719b4c/</url><position>Lead iOS Developer</position><locations quantity="1"><value>Kyiv</value></locations><salary>5400</salary><years_of_experience>6</years_of_experience><english_level>Upper Intermediate</english_level><experience /><skills quantity="76"><value>Design Patterns</value><value>iOS</value><value>MacOS</value><value>Matlab</value><value>Objective-C</value><value>OOP</value><value>Photoshop</value><value>REST</value><value>Scrum</value><value>Sketch</value><value>SQLite</value><value>SVN</value><value>Swift</value><value>Windows</value><value>XML</value><value>GCD</value><value>UIKit</value><value>Git</value><value>Xcode</value><value>CoreData</value><value>JSON</value><value>Jira</value><value>Multithreading</value><value>CocoaPods</value><value>Cocoa Touch</value><value>MVVM</value><value>CoreLocation</value><value>Clean Swift</value><value>xcode Instruments</value><value>Zeplin</value><value>Android SDK</value><value>MVC</value><value>REST API</value><value>Jenkins</value><value>RxSwift</value><value>Mobile app architecture</value><value>SwiftLint</value><value>CI/CD</value><value>FontAwsome</value><value>Remote notifications</value><value>Push-notifications</value><value>Notifications</value><value>SwiftCharts</value><value>ARC </value><value>Non-Arc</value><value>Sqlite3</value><value>MBProgressHUD</value><value>Swinject</value><value>Fastlane</value><value>RestFetcher</value><value>Alamofire</value><value>SSZipArchive</value><value>Crashlitics</value><value>AVFoundation</value><value>Android</value><value>Fabric</value><value>SOLID</value><value>MapKit</value><value>Autolayout</value><value>Foundation</value><value>Push Notifications</value><value>Firebase</value><value>Objective C</value><value>Networking</value><value>TestFlight</value><value>Sketch app</value><value>Localization</value><value>SnapKit</value><value>iOS SDK</value><value>SQL</value><value>Storyboards</value><value>Cocoa</value><value>Auto Layout</value><value>iOS Human Interface Guidelines</value><value>Continuous Integration</value><value>Swift/iOS</value></skills><highlights>EducationNational Aviation University, Kyiv Faculty of IT, Systems engineering. — 2013-2017 Bachelor degreeFaculty of IEM, Management of Foreign Economic Activity. — 2017-2019 Master Degree</highlights><expectations>•	Work in the good command•	To be the part of well working mechanism •	To be successful in the life•	To create something new that will make our world better</expectations></candidate>
<candidate id="17"><url>https://djinni.co//q/6600615bf9/</url><position>Marketing Manager</position><locations quantity="2"><value>Remote work</value><value>Ukraine</value></locations><salary>1500</salary><years_of_experience>4</years_of_experience><english_level>Intermediate</english_level><experience>Media buyerSmart project gmbhCreate and manage campaigns in Facebook for game advertising. Making tasks for creatives. Analysing and reporting on cpi, cpa, roas, revenue, ltv. PPC specialist from 11.2017 to 02.2019 (1 year 3 months) LivePage, Dnipro (SEO, PPC) Create, configure and manage projects in Google ads, Yandex Direct, Facebook, VK. Setup: Google Analytics, GTM, Yandex.Metrica, Facebook.Pixel, dynamic remarketing, Google Shopping, ecommerce. PPC specialist from 09.2015 to 10.2017 (2 years 1 month) WebGroup, Dnipro (SEO, PPC) Maintaining contextual advertising for projects in Yandex.Direct and Google Ads, setting up Yandex.Metrica</experience><skills quantity="6"><value>Digital marketing</value><value>Facebook Ads</value><value>PPC</value><value>Google Ads</value><value>Google Tag Manager</value><value>Google Analytics</value></skills><highlights /><expectations /></candidate>
<candidate id="18"><url>https://djinni.co//q/4714e4e81b/</url><position>Front-end Developer (React.js)</position><locations quantity="1"><value>Kyiv</value></locations><salary>800</salary><years_of_experience>1</years_of_experience><english_level>Intermediate</english_level><experience>developing new user-friendly features using React.jsoptimizing componentsworking with the product team and graphic designersworking with REST APIs</experience><skills quantity="13"><value>JavaScript</value><value>HTML5</value><value>CSS</value><value>SASS</value><value>Node.js</value><value>Gulp</value><value>PostgreSQL</value><value>React.js</value><value>React</value><value>Redux</value><value>HTML</value><value>Git</value><value>JSON</value></skills><highlights>Біля року займаюсь самоосвітою за напрямком Frontend розробка. Маю знання: HTML, CSS, Javascript, ES6, React, React-Redux, PostgreSQL. Вивчаю Node.js. В роботі використовую GIT. Маю виконані учбові проекти за вказаними вище технологіями. Пройшла курси: FreeCodeCamp, HTML Academy. Прочитала книжки: You Don't Know JS (K.Simpson), Learning React(Alex Banks and Eve Porcello)</highlights><expectations>Дружній колектив з можливістю особистого розвитку як спеціаліста</expectations></candidate>
<candidate id="19"><url>https://djinni.co//q/84a798b6d7/</url><position>Java Developer</position><locations quantity="1"><value>remote</value></locations><salary>2000</salary><years_of_experience>4</years_of_experience><english_level>Advanced/Fluent</english_level><experience>Profi.ru, Moscow – ICT online tutorOctober 2013 – now• taught students and young professionals using Skype and Teamviewer• advised on tasks solving on programming languages such as Java, Python, Bash, C, VBA, SQLFreelance Project Manager and DeveloperMay 2016 – August 2019• founded and headed project development and infrastructure using technologies such as Ubuntu, JS, Python, PhantomJS, MongoDB, MySQLSRG-IT Ltd., Moscow – Java DeveloperMay 2014 – May 2017 (3 years)• developed crawlers and parsers to extract data from real estate websites• provided my code with maximum coverage by Unit-tests• administered the system on a remote Unix-server• worked actively with databases on MySQL and MongoDB• coordinated with customers about data and reports provided• kept up to date project documentation in Confluence• wrote instructions for solving typical problems• participated in Agile teamwork style, scheduled time for tasks in JIRAOCRV Ltd., Moscow – DeveloperNovember 2011 – March 2013 (1 year 5 months)• developed real-time reports based on distributed data using Eclipse BIRT• prepared and uploaded large amounts of data to the database using the SOAP protocol• set up applications in the IBM Maximo railway assets managing system• wrote and edited database queries in Oracle DatabaseYandex Ltd., Moscow – Search Engine SupportNovember 2010 – July 2011 (9 months)• answered user questions about Yandex.Webmaster platform through an internal interface for processing incoming tickets• created tasks in JIRA and assigned tickets to developers</experience><skills quantity="21"><value>Java</value><value>Spring</value><value>Maven</value><value>Git</value><value>JUnit</value><value>SQL</value><value>OOP</value><value>Linux</value><value>JSON</value><value>HTML</value><value>CSS</value><value>XML</value><value>MongoDB</value><value>JIRA/Confluence</value><value>Python</value><value>Shell</value><value>PostgreSQL</value><value>IntelliJ IDEA</value><value>Jira</value><value>Hibernate</value><value>Bitbucket</value></skills><highlights /><expectations /></candidate>
<candidate id="20"><url>https://djinni.co//q/e3a6f06c75/</url><position>Team Lead Data Analytics / Senior Data Analyst</position><locations quantity="1"><value>Kyiv</value></locations><salary>4000</salary><years_of_experience>5</years_of_experience><english_level>Intermediate</english_level><experience>-построения команды аналитики с нуля;-создание dwh и репортинга;-участие в продуктовых процессах, проверка гипотез, тестов;-предоставление результатов  аналитики С уровню и командам продукта;- разработка kpi, nsm.</experience><skills quantity="13"><value>SQL</value><value>Databases: MySQL;</value><value>Analytical Thinking</value><value>Team Management</value><value>MS SQL Server</value><value>NumPy</value><value>Pandas</value><value>Python</value><value>MS Excel</value><value>Jupyter Notebook</value><value>BigQuery</value><value>Tableau</value><value>Data Presentation</value></skills><highlights>- построение команды аналитики  с 5 человек . Команда занималась анализом качества траффика и коммуникацией с внешними вендорами. Отдел вышел на показатель - закрытия стандартных ad hoc задач за один день и экономию затрат на контроль  качества траффика $20k.- создание аналитики проекта с нуля. Дневной/месячный репортинг, отслеживание kpi,  гипотезы по продукту , основанные на данных.- участие в создании dwh, сбор данных с 9 источников с одном месте, контроль технической реализации, оптимизация хранилища, имплементации продуктовой таксономии .</highlights><expectations /></candidate>
<candidate id="21"><url>https://djinni.co//q/b168e8f777/</url><position>JavaScript Developer</position><locations quantity="1"><value>Kyiv</value></locations><salary>4000</salary><years_of_experience>5</years_of_experience><english_level>Intermediate</english_level><experience>I have 5 years of experience in frontend development, including over 3 years of React/Redux development and half of year of development on Vue.js stack.</experience><skills quantity="20"><value>CSS3</value><value>Git</value><value>HTML5</value><value>JavaScript</value><value>LESS</value><value> SASS</value><value>Redux</value><value>REST API</value><value>GraphQL</value><value>STYLUS</value><value>webpack</value><value>Vue.js</value><value>React.js</value><value>eslint</value><value>ES6+</value><value>jQuery</value><value>BEM</value><value>Jest</value><value>SQL</value><value>Material-UI</value></skills><highlights>Moved a big e-commerce project to the new technology stack (ES6, Babel, Webpack).Reduced a load time of a complex ​SaaS web-​application.Developed few projects from scratch.</highlights><expectations>Professional growth.Interesting projects.Working with modern technologies and browsers (supporting of Internet Explorer isn't in my wish list).Projects on React are preferred.</expectations></candidate>
<candidate id="22"><url>https://djinni.co//q/1c790122/</url><position>SEO specialist</position><locations quantity="2"><value>Remote work</value><value>Ukraine</value></locations><salary>800</salary><years_of_experience>4</years_of_experience><english_level>Beginner/Elementary</english_level><experience>Опыт СЕО-специалистом свыше 4 лет. Имею ознакомительные навыки работы с CSS</experience><skills quantity="2"><value>SEO</value><value>HTML</value></skills><highlights>Вывод сайтов в топ-10 поисковых систем Google.com.ua, Google.kzТрафиковое продвижение сайтов в конкурентных тематиках (световое оборудование - ленты, лампы, подсветка (skyled.com.ua); изготовление металлоконструкций (steel-center.com.ua); наружная реклама (kreative-ag.com.ua); корпоративный отдых, тимбилдинг(corporative.org.ua)); как следствие - увеличение числа посетителей сайта и потенциальных клиентов по НЧ, СЧ и ВЧ запросам;- Ведение контекстной рекламы (Google Adwords) с показателем CTR&amp;gt;3%; как следствие - увеличение числа посетителей сайта и потенциальных клиентов</highlights><expectations>Работа с зарубежным рынком интернет-рекламы (SEO-оптимизация сайтов, контекстная реклама)</expectations></candidate>
<candidate id="23"><url>https://djinni.co//q/0b99408a/</url><position>Java Developer</position><locations quantity="2"><value>Remote work</value><value>Ukraine</value></locations><salary>3200</salary><years_of_experience>4</years_of_experience><english_level>Upper Intermediate</english_level><experience>Areas of expertise: Java;Hybris;ElasticSearch;JMS;Spring (IoC, MVC, Data, Security);JDBC, JPA, Hibernate, JSP, Maven;JUnit, Mockito;Log4j, Kibana;Jenkins;Tomcat, Jetty;Docker;AWS;SQL(MySQL, Oracle, MSSQL), OpenCV; HTML, CSS, Bootstrap;Skills: IntelliJ Idea, Linux command line;Development tools: Git, Jira;</experience><skills quantity="40"><value>AWS</value><value>Design Patterns</value><value>docker</value><value>Git</value><value>Hibernate</value><value>HTML</value><value>Java EE</value><value>Java SE</value><value>JDBC</value><value>Jetty</value><value>JPA</value><value>JSON</value><value>Linux</value><value>Maven</value><value>Multithreading</value><value>OOP</value><value>REST</value><value>Spring</value><value>Spring MVC</value><value>Tomcat</value><value>CSS</value><value>ElasticSearch</value><value>HTML5</value><value>Hybris</value><value>Jira</value><value>JMS</value><value>JSP</value><value>MySQL</value><value>OpenCV</value><value>Redis</value><value>XML</value><value>Java</value><value>REST API</value><value>Jenkins</value><value>Microservices</value><value>Spring Boot</value><value>JUnit</value><value>SQL</value><value>Hystrix</value><value>Solr</value></skills><highlights>- Setting up, launching and running dedicated development team. Development of services used by telecom industry leading companies. Building complex scalable project architecture and implementing solutions for handling huge amount of data.​Technologies used: Java, Spring Boot, Oracle, JMS.- Development of search engine for an online enterprise platform with millions of users based on Elastic Search. Running offshore development team controlled by in-house management and integrated into R&amp;amp;D ecosystem of the client. Actively participating in software development and delivery processes in the scope of the client's project.T​echnologies used: ElasticSearch, JMS (Hermes), JUnit, Mockito, Maven, Kibana.- Development of E-commerce Hybris-based product. Taking part in setting up and launch process of a local development team for US client. Working on implementation of back-end and front-end functionality.- Design and development of SOA product for insurance company. Building complex scalable project architecture and implementing back-end functionality. Technologies used: Oracle SOA, Web Services, Java.- Development and implementation of algorithms of dynamic video quality analysis based on Computer Vision technologies using best-practices of approaches in image and video handling.</highlights><expectations>Interested in part-time; flexible working schedule; nice skilled management</expectations></candidate>
<candidate id="24"><url>https://djinni.co//q/716a9360bc/</url><position>Senior Android Software Engineer</position><locations quantity="1"><value>Kyiv</value></locations><salary>5000</salary><years_of_experience>6</years_of_experience><english_level>Upper Intermediate</english_level><experience>Kotlin, Java SE, Bash, Groovy, GolangAndroid SDK and system components.Architecture: SOLID, patterns, MVP, MVVM, MVI, Redux.Databases and libraries: Room, SQLite, ContentProvider, Realm, DBFlow and ActiveAndroid.Network: OkHttp, Volley, Sockets, Retrofit (REST).Concurrency: Threads, Handlers (+Services), RxJava 1/2 + RxAndroid.UI: Design Support Library, custom views.Image loading and caching: Glide, Picasso, AUIL.Google Play Services: Maps, Account Login, Analytics.TDD: Unit testing (jUnit, Mockito), functional testing (Espresso).Other third-party libraries like ButterKnife, RetroLambda, GSON, AutoValue, Dagger 2 and so on.Video/Audio playback: ExoPlayer.Developer libraries: Timber, LeakCanary, Stetho.Gradle: custom scriptsCI (TeamCity, Jenkins, CircleCI), CD (Crashlytics).</experience><skills quantity="36"><value>AutoValue</value><value>Developer libraries</value><value>Gson</value><value>MVP</value><value>Retrofit</value><value>Room</value><value>SOLID</value><value>SQLBrite</value><value>SQLDelight</value><value>Glide</value><value>Java SE</value><value>Mockito</value><value>Picasso</value><value>Scrum</value><value>Services/Intent Services</value><value>Third-party libraries</value><value>Android SDK</value><value>DBFlow</value><value>DI (Dagger 2)</value><value>Fabric</value><value>Git</value><value>Gradle</value><value>JUnit</value><value>kotlin</value><value>RxJava + RxAndroid</value><value>SQLite</value><value>Synchronization</value><value>TDD</value><value>Espresso</value><value>GoF patterns</value><value>Google Play Services </value><value>Memory Management</value><value>OkHttp </value><value>realm</value><value>Transitions</value><value>View animations</value></skills><highlights>I have about 20 projects in my portfolio - from unknown and lost to apps with millions of active users.Wrote a bunch of automation scripts and programs in different languages (Kotlin, Groovy, Bash, Golang) for CI/CD, release management and code quality control.Brought in code reviews practice to the team.Developed and implemented CI/CD pipeline in the company.Active tech speaker.</highlights><expectations>Kotlin, interesting project, proactive team, new technologies, code reviews, testing, CI and flexible hours.I'm mostly interested in product-oriented company.</expectations></candidate>
<candidate id="25"><url>https://djinni.co//q/62df791f32/</url><position>QA engineer</position><locations quantity="1"><value>Kharkiv</value></locations><salary>400</salary><years_of_experience>0</years_of_experience><english_level>Intermediate</english_level><experience>Ищу первую работу. Готов заниматься тестированием чего угодно :)Обучался тестирование web , desktop , mobile приложений. Также работа с документацией внешней и внутренней. к сожалению рабочую Jira не довелось пощупать, знания только теоретические. Git знаю что да как , но на большим проектом не работал. SQL знаю достаточно, как мне кажется хорошо. Знаю что такое SCRUM и AGILE манифест</experience><skills quantity="14"><value>Manual Testing</value><value>Black Box testing</value><value>Test Documentation</value><value>Functional testing</value><value>non-functional testing</value><value>Regression Testing</value><value>Re-testing</value><value>Mobile Testing</value><value>Web Testing</value><value>Windows</value><value>SQL</value><value>Agile</value><value>Scrum</value><value>REST API</value></skills><highlights /><expectations>На чем работать значения не имеет, важны люди с которыми я буду работать. Ищу дружный коллектив. Отпуск две недели и больничный. А если будет какое-то обучение то я только за (английский или еще чего)</expectations></candidate>
<candidate id="26"><url>https://djinni.co//q/af6d290f21/</url><position>Sales Manager</position><locations quantity="1"><value>Kyiv</value></locations><salary>1000</salary><years_of_experience>10</years_of_experience><english_level>Pre-Intermediate</english_level><experience>- Управление продажами в регионах, разработка и внедрение региональной стратегии продаж.- Управление каналами сбыта.- Анализ рынка.- Развитие продаж на вверенной территории, контроль и обеспечение их выполнения.- Проведение переговоров с ключевыми клиентами, дистрибьюторами, региональными сетями, заключение договоров.- Управление дебиторской задолженностью.- Анализ цен и работы конкурентов.- Контроль над соблюдением цен и правильностью их применения, стратегия ценообразования в целом, внесение предложений по акциям, скидкам, распродажам и т.д.- Заключение, перезаключение контрактов на более выгодных условиях.- Обеспечение рентабельной, безубыточной деятельности вверенного региона;- Опыт ведения переговоров на высоком уровне.Поиск и привлечение новых клиентов;</experience><skills quantity="3"><value>Sales</value><value>B2B</value><value>Communication Skills</value></skills><highlights /><expectations /></candidate>
<candidate id="27"><url>https://djinni.co//q/f8af2e9b99/</url><position>Системный администратор</position><locations quantity="2"><value>Remote work</value><value>Ukraine</value></locations><salary>800</salary><years_of_experience>0</years_of_experience><english_level>Pre-Intermediate</english_level><experience>linkedin.   /in/alexey-volchenkо-9a2979146/</experience><skills quantity="8"><value>TCP/IP</value><value>HTML</value><value>Networks</value><value>Windows</value><value>Linux</value><value>Cisco</value><value>Networking</value><value>OCSInventory</value></skills><highlights /><expectations>Active Directory</expectations></candidate>
<candidate id="28"><url>https://djinni.co//q/b075c7069c/</url><position>Front-end developer</position><locations quantity="1"><value>Odesa</value></locations><salary>800</salary><years_of_experience>0</years_of_experience><english_level>Upper Intermediate</english_level><experience>Salesforce Commerce Cloud (SFCC, SFRA)</experience><skills quantity="33"><value>jQuery</value><value>AJAX</value><value>JavaScript</value><value>JSON</value><value>Git</value><value>EcmaScript 6</value><value>React / Redux</value><value>Vue / Vuex</value><value>Vue/Nuxt.js</value><value>SASS/SCSS</value><value>Bootstrap</value><value>CSS3</value><value>HTML5</value><value>REST API</value><value>webpack</value><value>Gulp | Webpack</value><value>HTTPS</value><value>es6</value><value>SASS</value><value>TypeScript</value><value>Webpack</value><value>Salesforce Development</value><value>SFRA</value><value>SFCC</value><value>OOP</value><value>Jira</value><value>ES6+</value><value>HTML</value><value>CSS</value><value>React</value><value>Babel</value><value>Gulp</value><value>German language</value></skills><highlights>Development and support of websites, implementation of new features using Salesforce Commerce Cloud (Demandware) platform:- Creating modules, templates, content assets and content slots using ISML, JavaScript/jQuery, HTML, XML, CSS, AJAX- creating new cross-browser and cross-device styles and templates based on PSD mockups- translation of business and marketing challenges into well-designed solutions- fixing style bugs for different devices and browsers- creation and maintain of code documentation- maintaining existing code, assets and troubleshooting issues- changing translations for different locales- web accessibility, keyboard management- work with collaboration tools such as JIRA, Confluence, Slack- collaborate with the team, client and Project Manager</highlights><expectations>Интересный проекты, новые задачи и технологии, постоянное всестороннее развитие.Interesting tasks and new challenges</expectations></candidate>
<candidate id="29"><url>https://djinni.co//q/4c67096307/</url><position>Data Scientist/ Machine Learning Engineer</position><locations quantity="6"><value>Kharkiv</value><value>Kyiv</value><value>Lviv</value><value>Odesa</value><value>Vinnitsia</value><value>Dnipro</value></locations><salary>3000</salary><years_of_experience>5</years_of_experience><english_level>Advanced/Fluent</english_level><experience>Test Engineer in Anvo-system Dresden GmbHApril 2019- nowAnvo-Systems Dresden specializes in highly reliable, monolithic non-volatile data storage system solutions in industrial and communication environments. My responsibilities as a Test Engineer include the multi-hierarchical testing of non-volatile memory chips during qualication process, modifying the Test Automation Software in C++ and implementing threshold control parameters, and performing statistical data analysis in Pythonto reach target eciency through the manufacturing process.</experience><skills quantity="7"><value>Python</value><value>C++</value><value>Linux</value><value>SQL</value><value>JavaScript</value><value>Artificial Intelligence</value><value>Functional programming</value></skills><highlights>- 8 years of professional experience in mentoring, research, and engineering - MSc degree with honours in Theoretical Physics from Heidelberg University in Germany- Extensive knowledge in analysis and computational physics- Skilful in coding and data analysis with C++, Python, and MATLAB- Skilful at using well-known libraries of Python (pandas, numpy) for handling data, scientific modelling, and problem-solving - Actively cooperating with research and engineering teams in Germany for working on projects related to image processing and machine learning.</highlights><expectations>I welcome to deal with your challenging tasks and projects. I enjoy both working in team and remotely. My areas of expertise are statistical data analysis, scientific modelling, and computing.</expectations></candidate>
<candidate id="30"><url>https://djinni.co//q/b334643bbb/</url><position>Front-end Developer</position><locations quantity="1"><value>Kyiv</value></locations><salary>1600</salary><years_of_experience>2</years_of_experience><english_level>Intermediate</english_level><experience>Coderiver fronted developer.• HTML, CSS templates implementation(Nunjucks, Pug/Jade, SASS/SCSS, LESS, Stylus)• JavaScript/JQuery• CSS animations, GSAP• Vue/Vuex, React applications• Teamwork• Communication with customers, designers</experience><skills quantity="12"><value>HTML5/CSS3</value><value>CSS3 Animation</value><value>SASS/SCSS</value><value>Jade/Pug</value><value>Nunjucks</value><value>AJAX</value><value>Gulp | Webpack</value><value>React</value><value>Vue / Vuex</value><value>NuxtJs</value><value>Git</value><value>es6</value></skills><highlights /><expectations>Flexible working hoursInteresting projectsProfessional growthGetting new skills and knowledgeFriendly team</expectations></candidate>
<candidate id="31"><url>https://djinni.co//q/2e4be21a01/</url><position>Middle front-end developer</position><locations quantity="2"><value>Remote work</value><value>Ukraine</value></locations><salary>2000</salary><years_of_experience>6</years_of_experience><english_level>Intermediate</english_level><experience>Experienced front end developer, worked mostly without frameworks, but had experience with Angular 2+/AngularJS/React.</experience><skills quantity="8"><value>Bootstrap</value><value>HTML5</value><value>CSS3</value><value>Git</value><value>JavaScript</value><value>jQuery</value><value>ES6+</value><value>Angular 2+</value></skills><highlights /><expectations>Interesting projects, friendly team, remote work</expectations></candidate>
<candidate id="32"><url>https://djinni.co//q/4b32da82/</url><position>PHP developer</position><locations quantity="1"><value>Odesa</value></locations><salary>1000</salary><years_of_experience>1</years_of_experience><english_level>Intermediate</english_level><experience /><skills quantity="28"><value>PHP</value><value>MySQL</value><value>Git</value><value>CSS</value><value>REST API</value><value>HTML5</value><value>MVC</value><value>OOP</value><value>HTML</value><value>Bootstrap</value><value>JSON</value><value>Nginx</value><value>Laravel</value><value>AJAX</value><value>jQuery</value><value>Wordpress</value><value>SOLID</value><value>Vue.js</value><value>JavaScript</value><value>Apache</value><value>Linux</value><value>Jira</value><value>RabbitMQ</value><value>Docker</value><value>PHPUnit</value><value>VueJS</value><value>Design Patterns</value><value>CSS3</value></skills><highlights /><expectations>Профессиональный рост</expectations></candidate>
<candidate id="33"><url>https://djinni.co//q/4e489141ea/</url><position>Digital Marketing Manager</position><locations quantity="1"><value>Lviv</value></locations><salary>800</salary><years_of_experience>3</years_of_experience><english_level>Advanced/Fluent</english_level><experience>I am a professional with vast experience and expertise in digital marketing and business analysis. I have worked with various small and mid-size companies and increased revenues from $0 to $10M+During the last years I have worked on and developed my skills in various fields of digital marketing.- Marketing. Naming, brand positioning. Producing creative ideas for brands and describing them.- SMM-marketing: positioning, revealing the target audience, pages management (Facebook, Instagram, Twitter, LinkedIn, Telegram), Facebook Ads- SEO-management: semantic core, SEO-texts writing and editing, linkbuilding, outer articles, Quora, Reddit and other methods- UX-writing: text models for websites implementing with designers and programmers- Copywriting: creative and informative texts for inner and outer articlesWhat job I search for:- Creative- Result oriented- Friendly teamContact me if you would like to fully transform your business to start generating higher profits.</experience><skills quantity="33"><value>Digital marketing</value><value>SMM</value><value>SEO</value><value>PPC</value><value>AdWords</value><value>Content marketing</value><value>Marketing Strategy</value><value>Social Media Marketing</value><value>Advanced English</value><value>Google Analytics</value><value>Facebook Ads</value><value>Google Ads</value><value>Web Analytics</value><value>Landing page optimization</value><value>Product Marketing</value><value>Ads Manager</value><value>Ads manager Facebook</value><value>Facebook</value><value>Twitter</value><value>Instagram ads</value><value>Linkedin</value><value>Market research and competitors analysis</value><value>Email Marketing</value><value>Entrepreneurship</value><value>Analytical Skills</value><value>Brand Strategy</value><value>B2C marketing</value><value>B2B marketing</value><value>B2B lead generation</value><value>Search Engine Marketing </value><value>Search Engine Optimization</value><value>Team management</value><value>E-mail marketing</value></skills><highlights>I have successful cases in which I increased revenue of the projects from $0 to $10M+1. Email marketing. In one month:- Mails opening - 150% increase- Link clicks - 125% increase2. B2C services website SEO/content strategy. In 6 months:- Leads quantity increase by 40 times3. B2B website SEO/content strategy. In 3 months:Pages per Session: 1,4 -&amp;gt; 8,9Bounce Rate: 77,46% -&amp;gt; 8,65%Avg Session Duration: 02:14 -&amp;gt; 03:05</highlights><expectations>I want to be a part of a goal-driven company that understands it's goals and</expectations></candidate>
<candidate id="34"><url>https://djinni.co//q/eab54fa6bf/</url><position>Web Developer</position><locations quantity="2"><value>Remote work</value><value>Ukraine</value></locations><salary>2000</salary><years_of_experience>3</years_of_experience><english_level>Upper Intermediate</english_level><experience>Develop and maintain the functionality of ERP system Identify and correct software deficiencies Superb debugging and problem-solving skills. Develop and maintain of Call Center Front-End Development with React Js, CSS and HTML. Simultaneously managing several projects. Provide guidance to other team members on web development issues.</experience><skills quantity="29"><value>MySQL</value><value>PHP</value><value>Git</value><value>JavaScript</value><value>OOP</value><value>Linux</value><value>REST API</value><value>jQuery</value><value>AJAX</value><value>MVC</value><value>Laravel</value><value>HTML</value><value>CSS</value><value>Bootstrap</value><value>JSON</value><value>SOLID</value><value>Redis</value><value>Nginx</value><value>PostgreSQL</value><value>Apache</value><value>XML</value><value>SQL</value><value>KISS</value><value>Webpack</value><value>HTML5/CSS3</value><value>jsavascript</value><value>phpstorm</value><value>SOAP</value><value>React.js</value></skills><highlights>I managed to be a team leader of call center program and develop and maintain several project at the same time with no problems.</highlights><expectations>I am interested in working with any kind of project.</expectations></candidate>
<candidate id="35"><url>https://djinni.co//q/7e8410d712/</url><position>Junior Project Manager</position><locations quantity="5"><value>Odesa</value><value>Kyiv</value><value>Lviv</value><value>Kharkiv</value><value>Dnipro</value></locations><salary>500</salary><years_of_experience>0</years_of_experience><english_level>Upper Intermediate</english_level><experience>Маю досвыд роботи у продажах працювала 1.5 роки в сервысному центры Мерседес-Бенз, проходила стажування у Neatpeek, на данний час працюю там. Маю велике бажання вчитися та розвиватися у данный галузі.</experience><skills quantity="1"><value>Project Management</value></skills><highlights>Я пишаюся тим, що працюючи на сервісі в досить короткий час зрозуміла сам продукт, та лилася в робочий процес. Пройшла стажування, та розвиваю свої навички я ЗЬ</highlights><expectations>Я хочу працювати в великій компанії, створювати та вдосконалювати продукт.</expectations></candidate>
<candidate id="36"><url>https://djinni.co//q/697bde7292/</url><position>digital marketing specialist</position><locations quantity="1"><value>Kyiv</value></locations><salary>1200</salary><years_of_experience>5</years_of_experience><english_level>Upper Intermediate</english_level><experience>•	Create and execute digital marketing strategy, driven by daily analytics and reporting geared at maximizing optimization of budgets•	Increase brand awareness by effectively managing online brand campaigns•	Experience managing paid advertising budgets, tools and resources (including external agencies)•	Monitor campaign pacing and performance to maximize effectiveness and efficiency of ad campaigns.•	Experience in conducting marketing researches•	Experience with customer segmentation, profiling•	Develop landing pages and other promo materials to support all marketing campaigns and initiatives•	Marketing materials development and promotion corresponding to corporate identity (brochures, leaflets, stands)•	Create content strategy and content to support marketing and sales activities, create and implement keyword •	Implementation of e-mail newsletters using the SendPulse service.•	Work with tech and sales to help write and present product roadmaps; writing technical specifications for the programmer •	Marketing materials development and promotion corresponding to corporate identity (brochures, leaflets, stands, gadgets)•	Events management (organizing business meeting, open doors meetings, corporate parties)•	Experience with the Google Advertising Universe (Google Ads, Google Analytics etc.)•	Experience using WordPress, specifically adding and updating content•	Experience with Google Apps (Drive, Sheets, Calendar, Docs)</experience><skills quantity="14"><value>Digital marketing</value><value>Google Analytics</value><value>Content marketing</value><value>Digital Marketing</value><value>Web Analytics</value><value>AdWords</value><value>Контекстная реклама</value><value>Brand Marketing</value><value>English</value><value>Marketing Strategy</value><value>Wordpress</value><value>Adwords PPC</value><value>Google Ads</value><value>PPC</value></skills><highlights /><expectations /></candidate>
<candidate id="37"><url>https://djinni.co//q/266cd460/</url><position>Head of Software Development, Senior Delivery Manager, VP of Engineering</position><locations quantity="1"><value>Kyiv</value></locations><salary>4500</salary><years_of_experience>10</years_of_experience><english_level>Advanced/Fluent</english_level><experience>I'm a seasoned manager in software development: project, people, product management. Administrative skill: outsourced software development office from scratch. Management of mixed remote teams (EU, Ukraine), verbal and written conversations with IT managers and customers. Team driving and motivation. Product design, vision, high-level requirements. Business trips to customers (US, EU).-- Solutions and domain areas in my projects are logistics (warehouse, yard, transportation), e-commerce, fintech (non-banking area, cashdesk, POS, payment system), electronic documents and payrolls, digital signatures, Linux (kernel drivers, networking), virtual infrastructure, cloud services.-- Team size: about 25 engineers and about 50 engineers under the line management. I can recruit and manage big teams of software engineers and experts of various specialties such as business analysts, project managers, solution architects, software engineers of any level, software testers, DevOps, etc.-- * Certified Scrum Master certificate. * ITIL Foundations for IT Service Management certificate. * Business and System analysis foundations.-- IT Project management: Azure DevOps, Jira for Software, Jira for ServiceDesk, Confluence, SWEBOK, SDLC, Agile, Scrum (CSM), Waterfall, PMBOK, BABOK, CMMI DEV, ITSM (ITIL).-- As a programmer in past, I'm familiar with Asm, C, C#/.Net Core, Pascal, Perl, Python, PHP, JavaScript, Shell, HTML/CSS, Java, C++, Golang, Rust, UML, SQL, various frameworks and platforms. I'm easily adapting to a new development environment, technologies and frameworks with no need for hands-on coding or micro-management.</experience><skills quantity="30"><value>Head of Software Engineering</value><value>IT Project Management</value><value>ITSM</value><value>Resource management</value><value>VP of Engineering</value><value>Agile</value><value>Delivery management</value><value>DevOps management</value><value>ITIL</value><value>People management</value><value>Process Management</value><value>Project Management</value><value>Scrum</value><value>SDLC</value><value>Jira</value><value>Confluence</value><value>Product management</value><value>Team management</value><value>Waterfall</value><value>Kanban</value><value>Risk management</value><value>Team Building</value><value>Team Management</value><value>Team Leadership</value><value>Agile Project Management</value><value>Requirements analysis</value><value>Office management</value><value>Azure DevOps</value><value>CTO</value><value>Director</value></skills><highlights>- Several software delivery offices are established from scratch;- Financial (cashdesk) system (fullstack JavaScript); - Online payroll system; - Electronic digital documents system; - Dev/prod infrastructure management (Docker containers); - Linux-based firewall (C/Linux, kernel modules);- Several E-commerce retail sites;- People management in outsourced IT (about 50 developers).* Certified Scrum Master certificate. * ITIL Foundations for IT Service Management certificate. * Business and System analysis foundations.* IT Project management.</highlights><expectations>Managing position in an international software development company (Head of Software engineering, VP of Engineering, Delivery Director, Delivery Manager or similar).</expectations></candidate>
<candidate id="38"><url>https://djinni.co//q/528fbe589f/</url><position>Junior+/Middle PHP Developer</position><locations quantity="1"><value>Kyiv</value></locations><salary>1500</salary><years_of_experience>1</years_of_experience><english_level>Beginner/Elementary</english_level><experience>Приймав учать у розробці , та здійснюю технічну підтиримку інформаційних порталів: 112.ua, 112.international, zik.ua,  5.ua, sbu.ua, omcf.org.ua та іньших меньш навантажених систем.    На даний час вивчаю symfony 4.x</experience><skills quantity="13"><value>MySQL</value><value>PHP</value><value>Git</value><value>Linux</value><value>jQuery</value><value>Docker</value><value>Yii2</value><value>Nginx</value><value>OOP</value><value>SOLID</value><value>JavaScript</value><value>AJAX</value><value>JSON</value></skills><highlights /><expectations /></candidate>
<candidate id="39"><url>https://djinni.co//q/e15cef65ad/</url><position>UI/UX DESIGNER</position><locations quantity="1"><value>Lviv</value></locations><salary>600</salary><years_of_experience>2</years_of_experience><english_level>Beginner/Elementary</english_level><experience>2018 - 2019 - Web Designer в компанії MagneticOne.2019 - 2020 - Midle Graphic Designer в компанії MiblArt.</experience><skills quantity="26"><value>Figma</value><value>Adobe Photoshop</value><value>User Interface</value><value>User Experience</value><value>Adobe Illustrator</value><value>UI/UX</value><value>WEB DESIGN</value><value>Prototyping</value><value>Sketch</value><value>Product Design</value><value>Photoshop</value><value>Illustrator</value><value>Graphic design</value><value>HTML</value><value>CSS</value><value>Vector Illustration</value><value>Mockups</value><value>Agile</value><value>UXUI</value><value>UX &amp;amp;amp; Analisys</value><value>Illustration</value><value>UX prototyping</value><value>Icons design</value><value>Sketch/Figma</value><value>Design Patterns</value><value>English</value></skills><highlights /><expectations /></candidate>
<candidate id="40"><url>https://djinni.co//q/ad92da4a91/</url><position>Junior seo</position><locations quantity="1"><value>Kharkiv</value></locations><salary>500</salary><years_of_experience>2</years_of_experience><english_level>Pre-Intermediate</english_level><experience>Начал изучение seo с работы копирайтером на фрилансе (около 2х лет), позже работал в паре с веб-дизайнером обучаясь у него всему, что касается поисковой оптимизации.На протяжении 4х месяцев заменял SEO-менеджера в компании flabers.comЗанимался линкбилдом, создавал технические задания для копирайтеров, собирал и кластерировал СЯ, проводил аудиты.Последние полгода работал в компании CryptoSoul.SEO, ASO - основные мои обязанности, также вел блог компании и занимался настойкой рекламы (AdWords, appleads)</experience><skills quantity="9"><value>SEO</value><value>Content marketing</value><value>Google Analytics</value><value>Digital Marketing</value><value>copywriting</value><value>google adwords</value><value>Social Media Marketing</value><value>E-mail marketing</value><value>SMM</value></skills><highlights /><expectations>В целом ожидаю от компании лишь интересных задач, пространства для обучения и достойной оплаты</expectations></candidate>
<candidate id="41"><url>https://djinni.co//q/874af32394/</url><position>Junior Front-end Developer</position><locations quantity="1"><value>Uzhgorod</value></locations><salary>1000</salary><years_of_experience>1</years_of_experience><english_level>Beginner/Elementary</english_level><experience>В основном занимался версткой страниц, сайтов и проектов, с применением небольшого фронтенда. Сейчас активно развиваюсь в сторону именно фронта и хочу постепенно уйти с простой верстки сайтов - именно на программирование. Работал как на фрилансе, так же и в компании.</experience><skills quantity="11"><value>JavaScript</value><value>HTML</value><value>SASS</value><value>CSS3</value><value>ES6+</value><value>SCSS</value><value>Git</value><value>CSS</value><value>Gulp</value><value>webpack</value><value>EcmaScript6</value></skills><highlights>Не знаю чем особо джуниор верстальщик или программист может похвастаться какими-то своими сверх работами. Могу прислать свое портфолио по проектам.</highlights><expectations>Хотелось бы найти команду в которой мог бы развиваться и в тоже время расти и применять новые знания и навыки в готовых, боевых проектах. Быстро обучаюсь и люблю свое дело.</expectations></candidate>
<candidate id="42"><url>https://djinni.co//q/03d3f86029/</url><position>web designer</position><locations quantity="1"><value>Odesa</value></locations><salary>500</salary><years_of_experience>1</years_of_experience><english_level>Beginner/Elementary</english_level><experience>Опыт работы графическим дизайнером — полтора года на фрилансе. Окончила курсы веб-дизайна в Projector Odessa, есть опыт работы над учебным проектом. Хорошие навыки коммуникации: опыт коммуникации с заказчиками, в том числе зарубежными (Upwork). Есть большое желание работать над более интересными и сложными проектами, развивать скилы в направлении UI-UX дизайна. Базовое владение After Effects. Уверенно владею инструментами Figma, Adobe Photoshop и Illustrator. При необходимости могу создавать несложные иллюстрации, иконки. Продолжаю работать над хард и софт скилами, осваиваю английский. Хочу работать над интересными проектами, будучи частью крутой команды. Не пугают сложные задачи и перспектива освоения новых инструментов в короткие сроки.</experience><skills quantity="12"><value>Figma</value><value>Adobe Photoshop</value><value>Adobe Illustrator</value><value>WEB DESIGN</value><value>Prototyping</value><value>UI/UX</value><value>Graphic design</value><value>Prototype</value><value>Photoshop</value><value>Illustrator</value><value>Adobe After Effects</value><value>Web Design</value></skills><highlights>На фрилансе было несколько интересных проектов по созданию айдентики, которые я считаю очень хорошим опытом.В рамках работы над итоговым проектом на курсе делала редизайн сайта отеля, заказчик остался очень доволен предложенным решением.</highlights><expectations>Моя главная цель — приобрести опыт, развиваться в выбранном направлении как хороший специалист.В идеале, хочу попасть джуном в крутую прогрессивную команду и работать под руководством опытных специалистов с перспективой вырасти в миддла и привносить свой вклад в проекты и развитие компании.</expectations></candidate>
<candidate id="43"><url>https://djinni.co//q/8b9ced47a0/</url><position>Marketing Manager</position><locations quantity="1"><value>Kyiv</value></locations><salary>1400</salary><years_of_experience>2</years_of_experience><english_level>Upper Intermediate</english_level><experience>Marketing Manager, Team Lead. Responsibilities: Managing the marketing department: tasks delegation and monitoring; Conducting meetings and brainstorming sessions for revising the tasks progress and creating new ideas for project development; Searching and working with external partners for community management in Asia and the USA; Working with the production companies to prepare the visual content; Managing the work of the outsourcing providers, partners;  Organizing technical courses in Ukraine and abroad for thecompany partners (Blockacademy); Supporting the brand strategy and positioning of the company;  Creating a marketing strategy to achieve the company's goals toencourage new customers and support the existing ones; Setting and implementing content strategy, social media andcommunication campaigns to align with marketing strategies;  Collaborating with the technical team for an accurateunderstanding of plans and product updates; Collaborating with the designer department to create visualcontent for the website, social networks, and blog; Tracking trends in marketing and digital technologies.Freelance, Marketing, and SMM manager: Preparing the company positioning and branding to enter a newmarket or to expand the presence on existing ones; Preparing the website structure and content materials due tomarketing practices and trends; Auditing the current company social presence to makeimprovements in positioning and branding; Preparing the content plan for social media and blog posts to setup the company’s social presence.</experience><skills quantity="7"><value>Marketing Strategy</value><value>Content marketing</value><value>SMM</value><value>Digital marketing</value><value>Brand Marketing</value><value>Social Media Marketing</value><value>Team management</value></skills><highlights>I have been working in the marketing field for the last 2,5 years. I started my career as a Community Manager at the blockchain startup and grew up to be a Marketing Manager and a Team Lead 1,5 years after. I managed a team of 4 people and we fully reconstructed the work of the marketing department at that time. Also, I was fully responsible for the blockchain courses and other events organization and promotion in Ukraine and Europe. As a freelancer, I have been working as a Marketing Coordinator for the project from the digital health sphere. I worked on the mobile application logic (customer journey map and optimization), on the website (funnels, content), on the positioning and social media plans. As a result, I made a marketing strategy for the project launch. On another freelance project, I have been auditioning the social media strategy for the honey company. I made positioning, content and communication plans for them. After implementing the proposed strategy the project increased its sales (at 3 times).</highlights><expectations>I am looking for a company that has real values along with a global mission, and for a project that is not afraid of creative and emotional campaigns.</expectations></candidate>
<candidate id="44"><url>https://djinni.co//q/7a416e85d0/</url><position>SEO Marketing Manager</position><locations quantity="2"><value>Remote work</value><value>Poland</value></locations><salary>800</salary><years_of_experience>4</years_of_experience><english_level>Upper Intermediate</english_level><experience>Developing and executing SEO strategies includes:- Keyword research, niche competition evaluation.- Review technical SEO issues- Optimize website content- Managing and scaling link building campaigns- Collect data and report on traffic and rankings- Close collaboration (tasking and performance control) with designers, programmers, copywriters- Experience with tools such as Screaming Frog, SEOquake, Ahrefs, Senuto, SurferSeo, Majestic etc.I also have experience as an affiliate manager. Responsibilities:- Managing members of affiliate program as well as identifying, recruiting new affiliates- Coordinating and executing targeted campaigns with different affiliate partners- Developing, maintaining and cultivating affiliate marketing relationships- Monitoring and reporting on customer satisfaction</experience><skills quantity="12"><value>SEO</value><value>on-page SEO</value><value>landing page development</value><value>Texts for landing pages</value><value>SEO Audits</value><value>SEO content</value><value>Analytics tools </value><value>Market research and competitors analysis</value><value>Linkbuilding</value><value>link building</value><value>Affilate marketing</value><value>Affiliate</value></skills><highlights /><expectations /></candidate>
<candidate id="45"><url>https://djinni.co//q/e3e6b408da/</url><position>Account Manager</position><locations quantity="1"><value>Odesa</value></locations><salary>750</salary><years_of_experience>1</years_of_experience><english_level>Advanced/Fluent</english_level><experience>— Negotiating with existing and recruiting new partners to network— Managing customers' requests— Maintaining statistics and reporting on each active client— Traffic analytics- Communication with customers on finance issues and Brand Safety issues- Customers' overdue debts reminders- Providing credit references- Communication with collecting companies</experience><skills quantity="38"><value>Communication Skills</value><value>English</value><value>International sales</value><value>It sales</value><value>Account Management</value><value>Lead generation</value><value>Sales</value><value>Presentation skills</value><value>Business development</value><value>B2B</value><value>Negotiations</value><value>Sales Management</value><value>Linkedin</value><value>customer support</value><value>B2B sales</value><value>Team management</value><value>Business Developement</value><value>Online Advertising</value><value>Europe and USA markets</value><value>fluent English</value><value>Team player</value><value>Jira</value><value>Customer relationship management</value><value>Customer service</value><value>Customer Support</value><value>customer success</value><value>Client Relationship</value><value>billing</value><value>mobile account manager</value><value>affise</value><value>mobile marketing</value><value>inventory optimization</value><value>Analytical Skills</value><value>Excel</value><value>Marketing</value><value>Networking</value><value>Affiliate Marketing and CPA networks</value><value>CPI</value></skills><highlights /><expectations /></candidate>
<candidate id="46"><url>https://djinni.co//q/f8e60ee33c/</url><position>Junior QA</position><locations quantity="1"><value>Zaporizhzhya</value></locations><salary>450</salary><years_of_experience>0</years_of_experience><english_level>Pre-Intermediate</english_level><experience>Прошёл курсы:1. Основы тестирования ПО.2. Основы тестирования игр.Ищу работу junior QA (manual).Готов учиться, развиваться.Уровень английского - средний. Прохожу два курса онлайн.</experience><skills quantity="14"><value>Manual Testing</value><value>Jira</value><value>HTML</value><value>Agile</value><value>Scrum</value><value>Java</value><value>Automated Testing</value><value>Android</value><value>MantisBT</value><value>Manual Testing </value><value>Regression Testing</value><value>Windows</value><value>iOS</value><value>Linux</value></skills><highlights>Курс "Основы тестирования ПО."Курс "Основы тестирования игр." Успешное завершение и получение сертификата.</highlights><expectations>Дружный коллектив, интересные разноплановые проекты, развитие и усовершенствование, ориентирован на долгосрочные отношения.</expectations></candidate>
<candidate id="47"><url>https://djinni.co//q/6fed550de7/</url><position>Junior Manual QA Engineer</position><locations quantity="1"><value>Kyiv</value></locations><salary>500</salary><years_of_experience>0</years_of_experience><english_level>Intermediate</english_level><experience>— Understanding of SDLC and bug life cycle;— Knowledge of different types and levels of testing;— Theoretical knowledge of main test design techniques;— Knowledge of testing methodologies and documentation types (test plan, test cases, bug tracking systems);— Understanding of Agile methodologies;— Knowledge and practical experience with HTML/XML/CSS;— Understanding of JSON data format;— Understanding client-server architecture and basic knowledge of networking protocols;— Basic knowledge of SQL and understanding of database structure;— Understanding TDD/BDD testing approach;— Basic knowledge of VCS (GIT)</experience><skills quantity="6"><value>Manual Testing</value><value>Quality Assurance</value><value>Scrum</value><value>HTML</value><value>CSS</value><value>ChromeDevTools</value></skills><highlights /><expectations /></candidate>
</candidates>